infinite-prosperity.com 2014-12-17

# Privacy Policy

## 

**  
Last Updated: 12th March 2014  **

Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. understands and appreciates that you, as an Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. website visitor, are concerned about the confidentiality and security of information that Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. may collect about you. Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. is committed to providing you with a range of investment resources and information on our services within a secure and confidential on-line environment. Our privacy statement sets out:

what information we may collect from you;

how your information may be used or disclosed;

the security of any information you provide;

cookies:  what are they and how are they used on this site;

acceptance and changes to Privacy Statements;

how you may access and correct your information;  and

how you can contact us.

## WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

The information that we collect about you will depend on the functions that you use within Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. We will not collect any information that identifies you as an individual unless you knowingly provide it to us.  Any personal information you supply will be used only in accordance with this Privacy Statement.  If you browse on this site, read or download information, our system will record the date and time of your visit, the pages viewed, and information downloaded.

## USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

Any information we collect from you via this site may be made available to (or used by) your adviser, any member of Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd., or any entity carrying out functions on behalf of Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. for:

the purpose of enabling Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. to provide products, services or information to you in accordance with your requests or reasonable expectations;

the purpose of enabling Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. to ascertain whether or not it has other services or products which may foreseeably meet your needs, and to notify you about these;

the purposes of enabling Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. research, planning, product development, risk assessment, risk modelling and marketing;  and

any other purpose required by or to the extent permitted by law.

We will only disclose personal information to third party entities carrying out functions on behalf of Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. on a confidential basis.  You should note that information we collect from you may also be disclosed to third parties if that disclosure is required (or to the extent permitted) by law.

## SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. takes reasonable steps to preserve the security of personal information it collects via this site.  

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed as totally secure.  Accordingly, although Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. strives to protect such information, Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk.  Once we receive your transmission, we take reasonable steps to preserve the security of information on our own system.  From time to time this site may contain links to other web-sites, and Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these web sites.

## COOKIES

A cookie is a small data file placed on your computer by the Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. server.  A cookie contains information about your visit to this site.  When you visit this site again, our server will look for the cookie and structure itself based on the information provided.  A cookie identifies your computer to our web server when you visit our site.  We do not use the cookie to store personal information about you.  It is recommended that you turn off any cookie warnings in your browser before using this site, otherwise you may not be able to use the full functionality of this site.

## ACCEPTANCE AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY STATEMENTS

You acknowledge and accept that your use of our site indicates your acceptance of the site terms and conditions of use of this Privacy Statement.  This Privacy Statement may change from time to time, so please check back occasionally.  Any information collected after an amended Privacy Statement has been posted on this site will be subject to the amended Privacy Statement.

## ACCESS AND UPDATING OF INFORMATION

You are able to access and update the personal information that we hold about you at any time.  To amend personal information that Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd. holds, you should contact your adviser.

## HOW YOU CAN CONTACT US

If you have any questions or feedback about this statement or any privacy issues concerning Infinite Prosperity Australia Pty. Ltd., please contact the Privacy Officer, Infinite Prosperity, PO Box 2478, Graceville East QLD 4075, Australia at any time in writing, or send an email to the Compliance Department.
